cashcannons.com 2009-08-01

# Home : DeltaSquadron | About DeltaSquadron

Thank you for visiting Delta Squadron's ("Delta Squadron") personal data management and e-commerce Internet web site ("Site") located at the URL www.deltasquadron.com. This Privacy Policy details certain policies implemented throughout Delta Squadron governing Delta Squadron's use of personally identifiable information provided to Delta Squadron via this Site. 

Privacy Policy Updates

Due to the Internet's rapidly evolving nature, Delta Squadron may need to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. If so, Delta Squadron will post its updated Privacy Policy on our Site located at www.ppcclassroom.com so you are always aware of what personally identifiable information we may collect and how we may use this information. Delta Squadron encourages you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of this Site will be subject to the then-current Privacy Policy. 

Information Collection and Use

You can generally visit our Site without revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself. However, in certain sections of this Site, to use certain services, we may require you to register for an account, or we may invite you to submit questions or comments or request information, participate in surveys, questionnaires or contests, subscribe to newsletters or participate in community forums. Due to the nature of some of these activities, we may ask that you complete and submit an online form with personally identifiable information such as your name, username, email address, contact information and credit card information. 

We may use your personally identifiable information to deliver certain services, products or information you have requested, verify your authority to enter certain password protected areas of the Site, send you notices for products and/or services that you have used or that may be of interest to you, and improve the content and general administration of the Site. 

If you are a registered user and post to any of the Site's community forums, other registered users of this Site may view your username and may send you emails, but they will not be able to see your actual email address. We may use your personally identifiable information to send you advertisements and other promotional information regarding our products and services or the products and services of our third party marketing partners and other communications related to the Site. 

Children's Privacy

Delta Squadron recognizes the privacy interests of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities and interests. No personally identifiable information is collected by Delta Squadron and Delta Squadron's services and Site are not intended for children under the age of 13. Delta Squadron does not target its services or this Site to children under 13. Delta Squadron does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. 

Cookies

We may use small text files called cookies to improve overall Site experience. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Cookies generally do not permit us to personally identify you. Cookies must be enabled for you to use certain areas of the Site. 

Advertisements that appear on this Site are delivered to users by our advertising partners. Our advertising partners may download cookies to your computer. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement. In this way, they may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. This information allows an advertising network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. Delta Squadron does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. 

Aggregate InformationThe Site may track the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, IP addresses, External Web Sites (defined below) linked to, and we may analyze this data for trends and statistics in the aggregate, but such information will be maintained, used and disclosed in aggregate form only and it will not contain personally identifiable information. We may use such aggregate information to analyze trends, administer the Site, track users' movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We may share this aggregate information with third parties to assist them in targeting advertisements to appropriate audiences. 

Disclosure

We may provide your personally identifiable information that we collect and the data generated by cookies to the vendors and service agencies that we may engage to assist us. For example, we may provide your personally identifiable information to an organization in order to complete a service (e.g., process your payment). 

We will also disclose your personally identifiable information if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority. We will not sell your personally identifiable information to any other company or organization except that we may transfer your personally identifiable information to a successor entity upon a merger, consolidation or other corporate reorganization in which Delta Squadron participates or to a purchaser of all or substantially all of Delta Squadron's assets to which this Site relates. 

Links to Third Party Sites

The Site may provide links to other Web sites or resources over which Delta Squadron does not have control ("External Web Sites"). Such links do not constitute an endorsement by Delta Squadron of those External Web Sites. You acknowledge that Delta Squadron is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and further agree that Delta Squadron is not responsible for the content of such External Web Sites. Your use of External Web Sites is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies located on the linked to External Web Sites. 

Security

We may employ procedural and technological measures, consistent with industry practice. Such measures are reasonably designed to help protect your personally identifiable information from loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. Delta Squadron may use encryption, secure socket layer, firewalls, internal restrictions, password protection and other security measures to help prevent unauthorized access to your personally identifiable information. 

Correction/Updating Personally Identifiable Information

Delta Squadron provides you with the ability to review, correct and delete any of the personally identifiable information that you have provided to us. If you wish to review or correct any information you have provided to us 

* You may access your account and review, correct and delete your personally identifiable information 

* Or you may contact us by email at: support@deltasquadron.com. If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy please contact us or via email at: support@deltasquadron.com.
